Do  you  believe  that  Iran  violated  the  peace  agreement  and  the  peace -fire
agreement?
Do  you  believe  that  Iran  is  still  committed  to  peace?
Yeah,  I  do.
They  violated  it,  but  Israel  violated  it,  too.
Are  you  questioning  if  Israel  is  committed  to  peace?
Israel,  as  soon  as  we  made  the  deal,  they  came  out  and  they  dropped
a  load  of  bombs,
the  likes  of  which  I've  never  seen  before.
The  biggest  load  that  we've  seen.
I'm  not  happy  with  Israel.
You  know,  when  I  say,  okay,  now  you  have  12  hours,
you  don't  go  out  in  the  first  hour  and  just  drop  everything  you  have
on  them.
So  I'm  not  happy  with  them.
I'm  not  happy  with  Iran  either.
But  I'm  really  unhappy  if  Israel  is  going  out  this  morning
because  the  one  rocket  that  didn't  land,  that  was  shot,
perhaps  by  mistake,  that  didn't  land,  I'm  not  happy  about  that.
You  know  what?
We  have,  we  basically  have  two  countries
that  have  been  fighting  so  long  and  so  hard
that  they  don't  know  what  the  fuck  they're  doing.
Do  you  understand  that?
I  don't  understand.